<clab:instance clab:definition="inside" clab:instance-name="cdi" clab:friendly-name="Inside page" xmlns:clab="http://clab.xmvc.org/ns/clab/1.0" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml">
	<clab:metadata>
		<clab:urlpath>/how-you-use-dnb-data/cdi-crm-mdm/</clab:urlpath>
		<clab:name>CDI/CRM/MDM</clab:name>
		<clab:child-for>
			<clab:component clab:definition="inside" clab:instance-name="how" />
		</clab:child-for>
		<clab:visible-for>
			<clab:component clab:definition="dynamic-nav" clab:instance-name="top-nav" />
		</clab:visible-for>
		<clab:clickable-for>
			<clab:component clab:definition="dynamic-nav" clab:instance-name="top-nav" />
		</clab:clickable-for>
	</clab:metadata>
	<clab:head>
		<clab:title>CDI/CRM/MDM | D&amp;B For Your Customers</clab:title>
		<clab:metatags />
		<clab:stylesheets>
			<clab:stylesheet>
				<clab:location>/inc/styles/cdi.css?<?php echo( md5( filemtime( realpath( "./inc/styles/cdi.css" ) ) ) ); ?></clab:location>
			</clab:stylesheet>
		</clab:stylesheets>
		<clab:scripts />
	</clab:head>
	<clab:mast>
		<clab:logo>D&amp;B</clab:logo>
		<clab:mast-title>D&amp;B For Your Customers</clab:mast-title>
		<clab:short-nav>
			<clab:instance-load clab:definition="navigation" clab:instance-name="short-nav" />
		</clab:short-nav>
		<clab:top-nav>
			<clab:instance-load clab:definition="dynamic-nav" clab:instance-name="top-nav" />
		</clab:top-nav>
	</clab:mast>
	<clab:page>
		<clab:heading>
			<clab:heading-caption>CDI/CRM/MDM</clab:heading-caption>
			<clab:heading-deco>guyleaningonwindow</clab:heading-deco>
		</clab:heading>
		<clab:content>
			<clab:column1>
				<clab:deco-stub />
				<clab:item-list>
					<clab:items>
						<clab:item>
							<clab:content><p>Help your customers to gain a complete view of their customers, integrate multiple information sources, and cleanse, match, and enhance customer and supplier data.</p></clab:content>
						</clab:item>
					</clab:items>
				</clab:item-list>
			</clab:column1>
			<clab:body>
				<h2>How you help your customers</h2>
				<p>Your customers are uncertain about the accuracy, completeness, currency, and cross-database consistency of their internal contacts and customer information, preventing them from confidently identifying and acting on sales and marketing opportunities within and beyond their customer base. You help them:</p>
				<ul>
					<li>To gain a single customer view to identify and act upon sales and marketing opportunities</li>
					<li>To have more insight on customer business relationships</li>
					<li>To work more efficiently and identify missed opportunities by resolving unknown entities in their databases</li>
					<li>To implement marketing and sales efforts much faster than they are currently able to</li>
				</ul>
				<h2>How <span class="dnbfyc">D&amp;B For Your Customers</span> helps you</h2>
				<p>Our solutions for customer and supplier data management enable a single customer/supplier view across multiple systems and touch-points. With a single customer view powered by D&amp;B's commercial insight, your customers can confidently deliver the right solution to <em>their</em> customers, maximizing revenue growth while achieving operational efficiencies.</p>
				<h3>The <em>extraordinary depth, breadth, and quality of our data</em> sets us apart.</h3>
				<ul>
					<li>The D&amp;B Global Database is the largest single source of local and global business data in the world, with information on more than 140 million global businesses in more than 190 countries.</li>
					<li>Our world-class DUNSRight<sup>®</sup> Quality Process—with more than 2,000 separate automated and manual checks, and data updated more than 1.5 million times daily—ensures insight that is accurate, complete, timely, consistent and, most importantly, actionable.</li>
				</ul>
				<h3>Our <em>database building and management capabilities</em> are one-of-a-kind.</h3>
				<ul>
					<li>Our patented Entity Matching technology and unique expertise enable you and your customers to effectively match and link similar data and maintain its quality over time.</li>
					<li>Our globally recognized D-U-N-S<sup>®</sup> Number acts as a key for data, provides continuity and consistency, and eliminates records duplication.</li>
					<li>Regular updates of our files are hosted by you at your facility, and are seamlessly integrated with your own data to create unique analytical solutions aimed at your customer base.</li>
					<li>Our Integration Manager software lets you bring powerful D&amp;B Entity Matching capabilities in-house, enabling you to provide enhanced business intelligence to your customers.</li>
				</ul>
				<h3>Our <em>uniquely qualified consultative team</em> has your back.</h3>
				<ul>
					<li>Specialized D&amp;B Relationship Managers have the expertise, insight, and flexibility to help you successfully integrate D&amp;B data and solutions into your offerings.</li>
					<li>Our one-touch dedicated “For Your Customers” customer hotline is at your service.</li>
				</ul>
			</clab:body>
			<clab:column2>
				<clab:phone-cta>
					<clab:instance-load clab:definition="blue-shadow" clab:instance-name="phone-cta" />
				</clab:phone-cta>
				<clab:mission-statement>
					<clab:instance-load clab:definition="blue-shadow" clab:instance-name="mission-statement" />
				</clab:mission-statement>
			</clab:column2>
		</clab:content>
	</clab:page>
	<clab:footer>
		<clab:copyright>© Dun &amp; Bradstreet, Inc., 2000–2009. All rights reserved.</clab:copyright>
		<clab:footer-nav>
			<clab:instance-load clab:definition="navigation" clab:instance-name="footer-nav" />
		</clab:footer-nav>
	</clab:footer>
</clab:instance>