<clab:instance clab:definition="inside" clab:instance-name="compliance" clab:friendly-name="Inside page" xmlns:clab="http://clab.xmvc.org/ns/clab/1.0" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml">
	<clab:metadata>
		<clab:urlpath>/how-you-use-dnb-data/compliance-and-enterprise-risk/</clab:urlpath>
		<clab:name>Compliance &amp; Enterprise Risk</clab:name>
		<clab:child-for>
			<clab:component clab:definition="inside" clab:instance-name="how" />
		</clab:child-for>
		<clab:visible-for>
			<clab:component clab:definition="dynamic-nav" clab:instance-name="top-nav" />
		</clab:visible-for>
		<clab:clickable-for>
			<clab:component clab:definition="dynamic-nav" clab:instance-name="top-nav" />
		</clab:clickable-for>
	</clab:metadata>
	<clab:head>
		<clab:title>Compliance &amp; Enterprise Risk | D&amp;B For Your Customers</clab:title>
		<clab:metatags />
		<clab:stylesheets>
			<clab:stylesheet>
				<clab:location>/inc/styles/compliance.css?<?php echo( md5( filemtime( realpath( "./inc/styles/compliance.css" ) ) ) ); ?></clab:location>
			</clab:stylesheet>
		</clab:stylesheets>
		<clab:scripts />
	</clab:head>
	<clab:mast>
		<clab:logo>D&amp;B</clab:logo>
		<clab:mast-title>D&amp;B For Your Customers</clab:mast-title>
		<clab:short-nav>
			<clab:instance-load clab:definition="navigation" clab:instance-name="short-nav" />
		</clab:short-nav>
		<clab:top-nav>
			<clab:instance-load clab:definition="dynamic-nav" clab:instance-name="top-nav" />
		</clab:top-nav>
	</clab:mast>
	<clab:page>
		<clab:heading>
			<clab:heading-caption>Compliance &amp; Enterprise Risk</clab:heading-caption>
			<clab:heading-deco>guyleaningonwindow</clab:heading-deco>
		</clab:heading>
		<clab:content>
			<clab:column1>
				<clab:deco-stub />
				<clab:item-list>
					<clab:items>
						<clab:item>
							<clab:content><p>Help your customers comply with anti-money laundering regulations, protect against fines, aggregate multiparty risk, and examine enterprise exposure to loss.</p></clab:content>
						</clab:item>
					</clab:items>
				</clab:item-list>
			</clab:column1>
			<clab:body>
				<h2>How you help your customers</h2>
				<p>Your customers need to develop a single, pristine view of total enterprise risk exposure. They could be subject to potential financial loss, reputation damage, process inefficiencies, and regulatory non-compliance. They need accurate insight on counterparties, the ability to monitor those companies, and the assurance that they are confidently complying with regulatory requirements around customer identity and risk aggregation.</p>
				<h2>How <span class="dnbfyc">D&amp;B For Your Customers</span> helps you</h2>
				<p>Our solutions for managing enterprise risk create a single, pristine view of client and counterparty entities and provide unparalleled data quality, timeliness, and business insight to enable confident enterprise risk management and compliance. Our solutions enable your customers to maintain accurate counterparty data, minimize financial loss, increase data cleansing and linking efficiency, protect their brand reputation, and enable current and future regulatory compliance.</p>
				<h3>The <em>extraordinary depth, breadth, and quality of our data</em> sets us apart.</h3>
				<ul>
					<li>We leverage the D&amp;B Enterprise Risk Repository, a powerful and dynamic globally linked database of legal entities and security counterparties.</li>
					<li>The D&amp;B Global Database is the largest single source of local and global business data in the world, with information on more than 140 million global businesses in more than 190 countries.</li>
					<li>Our world-class DUNSRight<sup>®</sup> Quality Process—with more than 2,000 separate automated and manual checks, and data updated more than 1.5 million times daily—ensures insight that is accurate, complete, timely, consistent and, most importantly, actionable.</li>
				</ul>
				<h3>Our <em>database building and management capabilities</em> are one-of-a-kind.</h3>
				<ul>
					<li>Our patented Entity Matching technology and unique expertise enable you and your customers to effectively match and link similar data (including legal entity data) and maintain its quality over time.</li>
					<li>Our globally recognized D-U-N-S<sup>®</sup> Number acts as a key for data, provides continuity and consistency, and eliminates records duplication.</li>
					<li>Valuable small business insight and hard-to-find private company information (55 million global private companies) is a key differentiator.</li>
				</ul>
				<h3>Our <em>uniquely qualified consultative team</em> has your back.</h3>
				<ul>
					<li>Specialized D&amp;B Relationship Managers have the expertise, insight, and flexibility to help you successfully integrate D&amp;B data and solutions into your offerings.</li>
					<li>Our Enterprise Risk and Compliance Specialists identify and validate unmatched customer input data, and bring a dedicated focus on interpreting and helping your customers act on compliance and enterprise risk insight.</li>
					<li>Our one-touch dedicated “For Your Customers” customer hotline is at your service.</li>
				</ul>
			</clab:body>
			<clab:column2>
				<clab:phone-cta>
					<clab:instance-load clab:definition="blue-shadow" clab:instance-name="phone-cta" />
				</clab:phone-cta>
				<clab:mission-statement>
					<clab:instance-load clab:definition="blue-shadow" clab:instance-name="mission-statement" />
				</clab:mission-statement>
			</clab:column2>
		</clab:content>
	</clab:page>
	<clab:footer>
		<clab:copyright>© Dun &amp; Bradstreet, Inc., 2000–2009. All rights reserved.</clab:copyright>
		<clab:footer-nav>
			<clab:instance-load clab:definition="navigation" clab:instance-name="footer-nav" />
		</clab:footer-nav>
	</clab:footer>
</clab:instance>