<clab:instance clab:definition="inside" clab:instance-name="credit" clab:friendly-name="Inside page" xmlns:clab="http://clab.xmvc.org/ns/clab/1.0" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml">
	<clab:metadata>
		<clab:urlpath>/how-you-use-dnb-data/credit-and-collections/</clab:urlpath>
		<clab:name>Credit &amp; Collections</clab:name>
		<clab:child-for>
			<clab:component clab:definition="inside" clab:instance-name="how" />
		</clab:child-for>
		<clab:visible-for>
			<clab:component clab:definition="dynamic-nav" clab:instance-name="top-nav" />
		</clab:visible-for>
		<clab:clickable-for>
			<clab:component clab:definition="dynamic-nav" clab:instance-name="top-nav" />
		</clab:clickable-for>
	</clab:metadata>
	<clab:head>
		<clab:title>Credit &amp; Collections | D&amp;B For Your Customers</clab:title>
		<clab:metatags />
		<clab:stylesheets>
			<clab:stylesheet>
				<clab:location>/inc/styles/credit.css?<?php echo( md5( filemtime( realpath( "./inc/styles/credit.css" ) ) ) ); ?></clab:location>
			</clab:stylesheet>
		</clab:stylesheets>
		<clab:scripts />
	</clab:head>
	<clab:mast>
		<clab:logo>D&amp;B</clab:logo>
		<clab:mast-title>D&amp;B For Your Customers</clab:mast-title>
		<clab:short-nav>
			<clab:instance-load clab:definition="navigation" clab:instance-name="short-nav" />
		</clab:short-nav>
		<clab:top-nav>
			<clab:instance-load clab:definition="dynamic-nav" clab:instance-name="top-nav" />
		</clab:top-nav>
	</clab:mast>
	<clab:page>
		<clab:heading>
			<clab:heading-caption>Credit &amp; Collections</clab:heading-caption>
			<clab:heading-deco>guyleaningonwindow</clab:heading-deco>
		</clab:heading>
		<clab:content>
			<clab:column1>
				<clab:deco-stub />
				<clab:item-list>
					<clab:items>
						<clab:item>
							<clab:content><p>Help your customers make credit approval decisions and manage portfolio risk, prioritize and maximize collections efforts, and monitor changes in credit risk.</p></clab:content>
						</clab:item>
					</clab:items>
				</clab:item-list>
			</clab:column1>
			<clab:body>
				<h2>How you help your customers</h2>
				<p>The wrong credit decision can cost your customers. They look to you to provide them with the insight they need to make credit approval decisions, manage their portfolio risk, and increase cash flow. They want to work with maximum efficiency and so need to prioritize and maximize their collections efforts. They also want to be proactive, and be able to monitor changes in the credit risk of <em>their</em> customers.</p>
				<h2>How <span class="dnbfyc">D&amp;B For Your Customers</span> helps you</h2>
				<p>We offer you the most trusted, comprehensive, and highest quality business-to-business risk data and solutions in the market today, along with the expert consultation you need to put it to work for you and your customers.</p>
				<h3>The <em>extraordinary depth, breadth, and quality of our risk data</em> sets us apart.</h3>
				<ul>
					<li>The D&amp;B Global Database is the largest single source of local and global business data in the world, with information on more than 140 million global businesses in more than 190 countries.</li>
					<li>Our world-class DUNSRight<sup>®</sup> Quality Process—with more than 2,000 separate automated and manual checks, and data updated more than 1.5 million times daily—ensures risk insight that is accurate, complete, timely, consistent and, most importantly, actionable.</li>
					<li>Our risk scores include insight based on more than 100 million accounts receivable records accessed through our unique Trade Reporting Program.</li>
				</ul>
				<h3>Our <em>database building and management capabilities</em> are one-of-a-kind.</h3>
				<ul>
					<li>Our patented Entity Matching technology and unique expertise enable you and your customers to effectively match and link similar data and maintain its quality over time.</li>
					<li>Our globally recognized D-U-N-S<sup>®</sup> Number acts as a key for data, provides continuity and consistency, and eliminates records duplication.</li>
					<li>Our unrivaled Corporate Linkage, unlimited in depth and breadth, enables your customers to aggregate relationships and credit exposure, even on private companies.</li>
				</ul>
				<h3>Our <em>uniquely qualified consultative team</em> has your back.</h3>
				<ul>
					<li>Specialized D&amp;B Relationship Managers have the expertise, insight, and flexibility to help you successfully integrate D&amp;B risk data and solutions into your offerings.</li>
					<li>Our Senior Risk Management Specialists bring a dedicated focus on interpreting and helping your customers act on risk insight.</li>
					<li>Our one-touch dedicated “For Your Customers” customer hotline is at your service.</li>
				</ul>
			</clab:body>
			<clab:column2>
				<clab:phone-cta>
					<clab:instance-load clab:definition="blue-shadow" clab:instance-name="phone-cta" />
				</clab:phone-cta>
				<clab:mission-statement>
					<clab:instance-load clab:definition="blue-shadow" clab:instance-name="mission-statement" />
				</clab:mission-statement>
			</clab:column2>
		</clab:content>
	</clab:page>
	<clab:footer>
		<clab:copyright>© Dun &amp; Bradstreet, Inc., 2000–2009. All rights reserved.</clab:copyright>
		<clab:footer-nav>
			<clab:instance-load clab:definition="navigation" clab:instance-name="footer-nav" />
		</clab:footer-nav>
	</clab:footer>
</clab:instance>