<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>
<cc:root xmlns:cc="http://www.xmvc.org/ns/cc/1.0" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml">

	<cc:config>
		<cc:dependency cc:type="inside" cc:instance="inside" />
		<cc:child-for>
			<cc:component cc:view="standard" cc:model="legal" />
		</cc:child-for>
	</cc:config>

	<cc:xhtml1-strict>
		<cc:head>
			<cc:title>Privacy Policy | Legal | Example Website</cc:title>
		</cc:head>
		<cc:inside>
			<cc:standard>
				<cc:heading>Privacy Policy</cc:heading>
				<cc:content cc:xhtml="1">
					<p>Example Website is committed to protecting individuals' right to privacy. By submitting your personal information to Example Website via the Site you are expressly consenting to Example Website's use of your personal information in accordance with the terms and conditions listed in this section.</p>
					<p>We use the personal information that you submit to us to provide you with the information you request, to contact you about news at Example Website and to obtain internal website tracking information that will assist us in developing our business and marketing strategies. In addition, your personal information may be used to protect Example Website against error, fraud, theft or damage to Example Website's property, to comply with the applicable laws and regulatory requirements and for any other reasonable purpose to which you consent. The personal information Example Website collects will not be used for any purpose other than that for which it was collected.</p>
					<p>The information we collect from you will be used, disclosed, stored, protected and disposed of in compliance with applicable privacy laws. We will not share or sell any of your personal information to any third party. The only exception is that your personal information may be disclosed on a limited basis to third parties retained by Example Website to assist with developing and maintaining our business.</p>
				</cc:content>
			</cc:standard>
		</cc:inside>
	</cc:xhtml1-strict>

</cc:root>