<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>
<cc:root xmlns:cc="urn:cc:root" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml">

	<cc:config>
		<cc:dependency view="inside" model="inside" />
		<cc:title>Terms of Use | Legal | Example Website</cc:title>
		<cc:child-for>
			<cc:component view="standard" model="legal" />
		</cc:child-for>
	</cc:config>

	<cc:xhtml1-strict>
		<cc:inside>
			<cc:standard>
				<cc:heading>Terms of Use</cc:heading>
				<cc:content xhtml="1">
					<p>Example Website makes available for your use on this website (the "Site") information, images, documents (collectively the "Materials") and various services (the "Services") subject to the terms and conditions set forth in this document (the "Terms of Use"). By accessing this Site you agree to the Terms of Use. If you breach any of the Terms of Use, your authorisation to use this Site automatically terminates and you must immediately destroy any Materials downloaded or printed from this Site. Any rights not expressly granted in these Terms of Use are reserved.</p>
					<h2>Use of Site Information</h2>
					<p>Except as otherwise indicated elsewhere on this Site, you may view, download and print the documents and information available on this Site subject to the following conditions:</p>
					<ol>
						<li>The documents and information may be used solely for personal, informational and non-commercial purposes.</li>
						<li>The documents and information may not be modified in any way.</li>
						<li>You may not remove the copyright notice: "(c) 2008 Example Website" or other proprietary notices contained in the documents and information.</li>
						<li>Example Website reserves the right to revoke the authorisation to view, download and print the documents and information available on this Site at any time, and any such use shall be discontinued immediately upon written notice from Example Website.</li>
						<li>The rights granted to you constitute a licence and not a transfer of title.</li>
					</ol>
					<h2>Copyrights: Limited Licence</h2>
					<p>The Materials and Services on this Site are protected by copyright and/or other intellectual property laws and any unauthorised use of the Materials or Services at this Site may violate such laws. Except as expressly provided herein, Example Website and its suppliers do not grant any express or implied right to you under any patents, copyrights, trademarks or trade secret information with respect to the Materials and Services and no portion of the information or documents on this Site may be reproduced in any form or by any means without the prior written permission of Example Website.</p>
					<h2>Trademarks</h2>
					<p>The trademarks, logos and service marks (the "Marks") displayed on this Site are the property of Example Website or third parties. You are not permitted to use the Marks without the prior written consent of Example Website or such third party that may own such Marks.</p>
					<h2>Third-Party Links, Downloads, Products and Services</h2>
					<p>This Site may provide links to third-party websites and/or may make reference to third-party products and services. Example Website makes no recommendations or endorsements about third-party products and services. Example Website is not responsible for the reliability of any data, opinions, advice or statements made on third-party sites, and makes no representations about their products or services.</p>
					<h2>Limitation of Liability</h2>
					<p>ALL MATERIALS AND SERVICES ON THIS SITE ARE PROVIDED "AS IS" WITHOUT WARRANTY OF ANY KIND, EITHER EXPRESS OR IMPLIED, INCLUDING, BUT NOT LIMITED TO, THE IMPLIED WARRANTIES OF MERCHANTABILITY OR FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE, OR THE WARRANTY OF NON-INFRINGEMENT.</p>
					<p>ANY MATERIALS DOWNLOADED OR OTHERWISE OBTAINED THROUGH THIS SITE ARE DONE AT YOUR OWN DISCRETION AND RISK AND WITH YOUR AGREEMENT THAT YOU WILL BE SOLELY RESPONSIBLE FOR ANY DAMAGE TO YOUR COMPUTER SYSTEM OR LOSS OF DATA THAT RESULTS FROM THE DOWNLOAD OF ANY SUCH MATERIALS. NO ADVICE OR INFORMATION, WHETHER ORAL OR WRITTEN, OBTAINED BY YOU FROM Example Website OR THROUGH OR FROM THIS SITE SHALL CREATE ANY WARRANTY NOT EXPRESSLY STATED IN THE TERMS OF USE.</p>
					<h2>Indemnity</h2>
					<p>You agree to indemnify and hold Example Website and its subsidiaries, affiliates, officers, agents, co-branders or other partners and employees harmless from any claim or demand, including reasonable attorneys' fees, made by any third party due to or arising out of content you submit, post to or transmit through this Site, your use of this Site, your connection to this Site, your violation of the Terms of Use or your violation of any rights of another person or entity.</p>
				</cc:content>
			</cc:standard>
		</cc:inside>
	</cc:xhtml1-strict>

</cc:root>