<clab:instance xmlns:clab="http://clab.xmvc.org/ns/clab/1.0" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" clab:definition="inside" clab:instance-name="business" clab:friendly-name="Inside page">
	<clab:metadata>
		<clab:urlpath>/how-you-use-dnb-data/business-intelligence-and-analytics/</clab:urlpath>
		<clab:name>Business Intelligence &amp; Analytics</clab:name>
		<clab:child-for>
			<clab:component clab:definition="inside" clab:instance-name="how"/>
		</clab:child-for>
		<clab:visible-for>
			<clab:component clab:definition="dynamic-nav" clab:instance-name="top-nav"/>
		</clab:visible-for>
		<clab:clickable-for>
			<clab:component clab:definition="dynamic-nav" clab:instance-name="top-nav"/>
		</clab:clickable-for>
	</clab:metadata>
	<clab:head>
		<clab:title>Business Intelligence &amp; Analytics | D&amp;B For Your Customers</clab:title>
		<clab:metatags/>
		<clab:stylesheets>
			<clab:stylesheet>
				<clab:location>/inc/styles/business.css?<?php echo( md5( filemtime( realpath( "./inc/styles/business.css" ) ) ) ); ?></clab:location>
			</clab:stylesheet>
		</clab:stylesheets>
		<clab:scripts/>
	</clab:head>
	<clab:mast>
		<clab:logo>D&amp;B</clab:logo>
		<clab:mast-title>D&amp;B For Your Customers</clab:mast-title>
		<clab:short-nav>
			<clab:instance-load clab:definition="navigation" clab:instance-name="short-nav"/>
		</clab:short-nav>
		<clab:top-nav>
			<clab:instance-load clab:definition="dynamic-nav" clab:instance-name="top-nav"/>
		</clab:top-nav>
	</clab:mast>
	<clab:page>
		<clab:heading>
			<clab:heading-caption>Business Intelligence &amp; Analytics</clab:heading-caption>
			<clab:heading-deco>guyleaningonwindow</clab:heading-deco>
		</clab:heading>
		<clab:content>
			<clab:column1>
				<clab:deco-stub/>
				<clab:item-list>
					<clab:items>
						<clab:item>
							<clab:content>
<p>Help your customers evaluate potential markets; cleanse, enhance, and create customer databases; market to customers; and understand customer value and behavior.</p></clab:content>
						</clab:item>
					</clab:items>
				</clab:item-list>
			</clab:column1>
			<clab:body>
				<h2>How you help your customers</h2>
				<p>Your customers require business intelligence to evaluate potential new markets and aasdasd campaigns. They need to cleanse, enhance, and create solid customer databases to fuel their sales and marketing activities, and learn how best to market to those customers once they've found them. They also need to understand the relative value of each of their customers, and understand how customer behavior can help inform their sales approach.</p>
				<h2>How <span class="dnbfyc">D&amp;B For Your Customers</span> helps you</h2>
				<p>Our unique data and analytics will give your customers the insight they need. With unparalleled depth and easy integration into your systems and processes, your customers will rely on you for current, accurate business intelligence, analytics, and insight.</p>
				<h3>The <em>extraordinary depth, breadth, and quality of our data</em> sets us apart.</h3>
				<ul>
					<li>The D&amp;B Global Database is the largest single source of local and global business data in the world, with information on more than 140 million global businesses in more than 190 countries.</li>
					<li>Our world-class DUNSRight<sup>®</sup> Quality Process—with more than 2,000 separate automated and manual checks, and data updated more than 1.5 million times daily—ensures insight that is accurate, complete, timely, consistent and, most importantly, actionable.</li>
					<li>Our huge breadth of firmographic and behavioral data helps your customers make decisions with confidence.</li>
				</ul>
				<h3>Our <em>database building and management capabilities</em> are one-of-a-kind.</h3>
				<ul>
					<li>Our patented Entity Matching technology and unique expertise enable you and your customers to effectively match and link similar data and maintain its quality over time.</li>
					<li>Our globally recognized D-U-N-S<sup>®</sup> Number acts as a key for data, provides continuity and consistency, and eliminates records duplication.</li>
					<li>Regular updates of our files are hosted by you at your facility, and are seamlessly integrated with your own data to create unique analytical solutions aimed at your customer base.</li>
					<li>Our Integration Manager software lets you bring powerful D&amp;B Entity Matching capabilities in-house, enabling you to provide enhanced business intelligence to your customers.</li>
				</ul>
				<h3>Our <em>uniquely qualified consultative team</em> has your back.</h3>
				<ul>
					<li>Specialized D&amp;B Relationship Managers have the expertise, insight, and flexibility to help you successfully integrate D&amp;B data and solutions into your offerings.</li>
					<li>Our Business Intelligence Analysts understand what's needed for sound decisions.</li>
					<li>Our one-touch dedicated “For Your Customers” customer hotline is at your service.</li>
				</ul>
			</clab:body>
			<clab:column2>
				<clab:phone-cta>
					<clab:instance-load clab:definition="blue-shadow" clab:instance-name="phone-cta"/>
				</clab:phone-cta>
				<clab:mission-statement>
					<clab:instance-load clab:definition="blue-shadow" clab:instance-name="mission-statement"/>
				</clab:mission-statement>
			</clab:column2>
		</clab:content>
	</clab:page>
	<clab:footer>
		<clab:copyright>© Dun &amp; Bradstreet, Inc., 2003–2009. All rights reserved.</clab:copyright>
		<clab:footer-nav>
			<clab:instance-load clab:definition="navigation" clab:instance-name="footer-nav"/>
		</clab:footer-nav>
	</clab:footer>
</clab:instance>