<clab:instance xmlns:clab="http://clab.xmvc.org/ns/clab/1.0" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" clab:definition="inside" clab:instance-name="working" clab:friendly-name="Inside page">
	<clab:metadata>
		<clab:urlpath>/working-with-dnb/</clab:urlpath>
		<clab:name>Working with D&amp;B</clab:name>
		<clab:sort-index>2</clab:sort-index>
		<clab:visible-for>
			<clab:component clab:definition="dynamic-nav" clab:instance-name="top-nav"/>
		</clab:visible-for>
		<clab:clickable-for>
			<clab:component clab:definition="dynamic-nav" clab:instance-name="top-nav"/>
		</clab:clickable-for>
	</clab:metadata>
	<clab:head>
		<clab:title>Working with D&amp;B | D&amp;B For Your Customers</clab:title>
		<clab:metatags/>
		<clab:stylesheets>
			<clab:stylesheet>
				<clab:location>/inc/styles/working.css?<?php echo( md5( filemtime( realpath( "./inc/styles/working.css" ) ) ) ); ?></clab:location>
			</clab:stylesheet>
		</clab:stylesheets>
		<clab:scripts/>
	</clab:head>
	<clab:mast>
		<clab:logo>D&amp;B</clab:logo>
		<clab:mast-title>D&amp;B For Your Customers</clab:mast-title>
		<clab:short-nav>
			<clab:instance-load clab:definition="navigation" clab:instance-name="short-nav"/>
		</clab:short-nav>
		<clab:top-nav>
			<clab:instance-load clab:definition="dynamic-nav" clab:instance-name="top-nav"/>
		</clab:top-nav>
	</clab:mast>
	<clab:page>
		<clab:heading>
			<clab:heading-caption>Working with D&amp;B</clab:heading-caption>
			<clab:heading-deco>guyleaningonwindow</clab:heading-deco>
		</clab:heading>
		<clab:content>
			<clab:column1>
				<clab:deco-stub/>
				<clab:item-list>
					<clab:items>
						<clab:item>
							<clab:content>
                <p>We've made it easy to work with D&amp;B to build better solutions and services for your customers.</p>
              </clab:content>
						</clab:item>
					</clab:items>
				</clab:item-list>
			</clab:column1>
			<clab:body>
				<h2>Working with D&amp;B</h2>
				<p>We've made it easy to work with D&amp;B to build better solutions and services for your customers.</p>

				<h3><strong>Step 1. Contact</strong></h3>
				<p>When you request information or ask to be contacted by us, you will hear from a dedicated Relationship Manager within 24 hours. Your Relationship Manager is selected based on your needs, will have expertise in your specific area of business, and is solely focused on partner relationships—that's all they do.  To keep it easy for you, your Relationship Manager will be your single point of contact with D&amp;B.</p>

				<h3><strong>Step 2. Exploration</strong></h3>
				<p>The first meetings are dedicated to understanding your business—and even personal—objectives; our success is based on your success.   We'll talk about your overall objectives and measures of success, the types of customers you serve, the type of business information you require, how the data will be displayed, and your revenue model using D&amp;B insight.</p>

				<h3><strong>Step 3. Demonstration</strong></h3>
				<p>Once we understand your objectives and have prepared recommendations for your solution based on your identified needs, it's time to show you how it works. You'll learn more details about the data and insight we can provide, and, if applicable, we'll demonstrate how that data powers relevant D&amp;B solutions. We also help you understand the power of our data, including our DUNSRight<sup>®</sup> Quality Process, so that you feel confident with the data and can answer any questions from your customers.</p>

				<h3><strong>Step 4. Agreement</strong></h3>
				<p>Once we've determined and demonstrated your solution (and assuming that it meets your needs), we then work with you to create a clear Agreement that will include terms, economics, branding, etc.</p>

				<h3><strong>Step 5. Fulfillment</strong></h3>
				<p>Our Fulfillment team will work with you to ensure that you receive your data solution on time and in the form you require.  Our Fulfillment experts will also work directly with your technology and data teams as required.</p>

				<h3><strong>Step 6. Post-Sales Support</strong></h3>
				<p>After you receive your data solution, our goal is to ensure that it meets your requirements and helps you to achieve your objectives.  Along with direct follow-up from your Relationship Manager, you also have access to our dedicated Customer Service hotline and Web site.</p>
			</clab:body>
			<clab:column2>
				<clab:phone-cta>
					<clab:instance-load clab:definition="blue-shadow" clab:instance-name="phone-cta"/>
				</clab:phone-cta>
				<clab:mission-statement>
					<clab:instance-load clab:definition="blue-shadow" clab:instance-name="mission-statement"/>
				</clab:mission-statement>
			</clab:column2>
		</clab:content>
	</clab:page>
	<clab:footer>
		<clab:copyright>© Dun &amp; Bradstreet, Inc., 2000–2009. All rights reserved.</clab:copyright>
		<clab:footer-nav>
			<clab:instance-load clab:definition="navigation" clab:instance-name="footer-nav"/>
		</clab:footer-nav>
	</clab:footer>
</clab:instance>